Guide to the Preservation Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Preservation Department records, 1947-2002; Accession 2008-A-165
  - Preservation Records / Preservation Process
    - History of Preservation at Yale -- ["Gays [sic] Early Files Box 1" also written on folder], 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 300)
  - Records (e.g., Cataloging)
    - Brittle Books, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Cataloging Films, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - Copyright, 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Yale University Catalog Department Manual, March 1979 [loose-leaf binder], 1952-1986 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - Statistics, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - Uncataloged Collections, Undated (Box 22, Folder 306)
    - Yale -- RLG Preservation, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 307)
    - PCR's -- RLG, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 308)
    - RLG -- PCR Survey, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 309)
    - Brittle -- SML Survey, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 310)
    - Gay's RLIN Folder, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Director's Memos and Reports
    - Cunha, Geo. Daniel [preservation consultant], 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - IFLA Conservation Section, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - Memoranda, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Memoranda -- Notes, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - Materials, Library, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - LC Filming [combination of reference, personnel, budget, and correspondence], 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - Memos -- Yale, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - Flood Manual, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - Fires, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 384)
    - Floods, 1984-1985, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - Fire Alarms, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - [loose pages -- miscellaneous Yale memoranda on materials and methods, labels, policies, 1978, 1981, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Evaluation Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 387)
    - Preservation Training -- SML, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - Policies [miscellaneous files on a variety of subjects], 1972-1979, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 389)
    - PS [ Public Services] Libn's Conf., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 390)
    - Conservation Division, 1973, 1982-1990 (Box 8, Folder 391)
    - Blank Floor Plans, 1965, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 392)
    - Moves, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 393)
    - Microfilm, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 394)
    - Microfilm Pricing, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - CLR Binding Miscellaneous Files
    - CLR, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - CLR -- Binding, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Comm. [Commercial] Binding Script, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Comm. [Commercial] Binding Script, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - Comm. Binding Manual, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - CLR Advisory Council 3/2/87 LC Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - CLR Paper Meeting Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - CLR -- Paper Report, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - CLR Paper Stds. [Standards] -- Current, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Miscellaneous Subject Files, Preservation Topics, 1989-1993
    - ARL Preservation, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 406)
    - CLR Committion Preservation and Access, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 407)
    - CLR Committion Preservation and Access, 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 408)
    - CLR Commission on Preservation, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 409)
    - Connecticut, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 410)
    - CONSER Multiple Versions, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 411)
    - Copyright, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 412)
    - COSI Committee on Scholarly Information, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 413)
    - Deacidification, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 414)
    - Deacidification, 1993, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 415)
    - Bookkeeper, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 416)
    - Mass Deacidification Seminar, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - Disaster Stanford, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 418)
    - Disasters, 1983, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 419)
    - Disaster Control, Undated (Box 10, Folder 420)
    - Disaster Planner, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - Disaster Preparation, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Disaster Recovery, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Harvard University, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - Historic Preservation in Conn., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - Isoperms (sebara), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 426)
    - MAPS, Undated (Box 10, Folder 427)
    - MARC subfield M, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 428)
    - Merrill - Oldham, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 429)
    - Microform, Inc., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 430)
    - Museum Computer Network, Undated (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - National Library of Medicine News, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 432)
    - Use Based Project Approach, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 433)
    - NEH-Grant Reviews PS-Z0634 (Expert System), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 434)
    - NEH Guidelines, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 435)
    - NEWS National Endowment for the Humanities, Undated (Box 10, Folder 436)
    - New York Public Library, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 437)
    - NHPRC - National Historical Publications and Records Commission, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 439)
    - RBMS Newsletter, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 440)
    - RLG Conference, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 441)
    - RLG Preserv, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    - RLG Symposium, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - Catalog of RLG Activities and Projects in, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 445)
  - Subject Files
    - Conservation - Equipment, 1986, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Conservation Grant Proposal (Berkeley), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - Conspectus, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 448)
    - Conspectus Article for arl/dms, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    - Conspectus in Preservation Planning, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Conspectus - Yale, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - Contract for RLG, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - Cooperative Efforts "Programs" "Projects", 1984 (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - Copiers, 1981, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - CopyFlo, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Correspondence A, B, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Correspondence C, D, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Correspondence D,E,F, 1982-1988 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - Correspondence G,H,I, 1980-1988 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Correspondence I, J, 1982-1989 (Box 11, Folder 460)
    - Correspondence K,L, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - Correspondence M,N, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - Correspondence O,P, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - Correspondence Q,R,S, 1980-1989 (Box 11, Folder 464)
    - Correspondence T,U,V, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 465)
    - Correspondence W,X,Y,Z, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 466)
    - Costs, 1983, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 467)
    - CPMP, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 468)
    - CRL, 1991, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 469)
    - Cradle Microfilming, Undated (Box 11, Folder 470)
    - Crawford Theatre Collection, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 471)
    - CT State Library, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 472)
    - CT State Preservation Plan, 1988, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 473)
    - D'Annuncio, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 474)
    - DARL, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 475)
    - DEZ, 1983-1992 (Box 11, Folder 476)
    - Degradation of Papers Papers, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 477)
    - Dehumidifier / Water Soaked Books, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 478)
    - Dictionaries of Preservation Terms, Undated (Box 11, Folder 480)
    - Digitization, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 481)
    - Disreputable Reprinters, Undated (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - Distribution of Microfilms, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - Education (in conservation), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 484)
    - Education (in preservation), 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - Electronic Mail, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - Emergencies, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 487)
    - Environmental Survey, Undated (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - Equipment, 1983-1989 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - Exhibits, undated (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - Exhibit: Conservation/Pres. 2/81, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - Expensive Items, 1985-1988 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - Film Bases, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 493)
    - Flowcharts, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 495)
    - Folios - Atlases, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 496)
    - Foreign Pres., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 497)
    - Forms - Searching, etc., 1971 (Box 12, Folder 498)
    - Freeze-drying, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 499)
    - Freezing, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 500)
    - Fumigation, 1976, 1983, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 501)
    - Fumigation - LC and Yale, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 502)
    - Future in Preservation Microfilming, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 505)
    - Gamma Radiation, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 506)
    - Garland Pres. Reprints, 1984-1991 (Box 12, Folder 507)
    - GEAC, 1979-1989 (Box 12, Folder 508)
    - Getty, 1988, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 509)
    - Gifts, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 510)
    - Government Documents, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 511)
    - Grant Planning, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 512)
    - Grants, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 514)
    - Grip-tite / pink strings, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 516)
    - Harvard - RLG Preservation (Walker), 1970, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 517)
    - Harvard Pres. - Walker, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 518)
    - Hayes Study Preservation, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 519)
    - Hazards, Undated (Box 12, Folder 520)
    - History Seminar, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 521)
    - Historical Sound Recording, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Humanities Research Center, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - ICI, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 524)
    - IDC, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 525)
    - IFLA, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 526)
    - IFLA Serials Preservation, 1988, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 527)
    - I.L.L. (Interlibrary Loan for Libraries, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 528)
    - Illustrations, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 529)
    - Image Prints, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 530)
    - Income, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 531)
    - Indiana University, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 532)
    - Injury - Department Heads Report, Undated (Box 12, Folder 533)
    - Ink, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 534)
    - Library Insurance, Undated (Box 12, Folder 535)
    - Interviews, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 536)
    - Interviewing, Undated (Box 12, Folder 537)
    - IPC - (Institute for Paper Chemistry), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 538)
    - IPI, Undated (Box 12, Folder 539)
    - IPL, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 540)
    - ISO Standards (Microfilm), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 541)
    - Japan (Pres.), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 542)
    - Jobs, 1983-1992 (Box 12, Folder 543)
    - Juvenilice, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 544)
    - Kantor Microfilm Cost Study, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 545)
    - Kresse, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 546)
    - Keys, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 547)
    - Kohut, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 548)
    - Labeling Systems, 1986, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 549)
    - Law Library, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 550)
    - Legislative Hearing, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 551)
    - Libraries at Yale, Undated (Box 12, Folder 552)
    - Lithium Corp, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 553)
    - Lost Cause Press, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 554)
    - Lowell File, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 555)
    - LRTS Articles - Tate, 1980, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 556)
    - Mail / Letterheads, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 557)
    - Management, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 558)
    - Management Training, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 559)
    - Manuscripts (Preservation), Undated (Box 12, Folder 560)
    - MAP Resources Group and Report, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 561)
    - Maps, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 562)
    - Maps Mid-Atlantic Pres., 1988, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 563)
    - Master Negatives, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 564)
    - Medical Library, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 565)
    - Medicine, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 566)
    - Metro, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 567)
    - Micro Technologies, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 568)
    - Micro Computers, 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 569)
    - Microfiche, 1986, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 570)
    - Microfiche Supplies and Equipment, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 571)
    - Microfilm Bases, Undated (Box 13, Folder 572)
    - Microfilm Cataloging, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 573)
    - Microfilm Deterioration, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 574)
    - Microfilm Equipment, 1985, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 575)
    - Microfilm Master, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 576)
    - Microfilm Over Optical, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 577)
    - Microfilm Permanence, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 578)
    - Microfilm Storage, 1989, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 579)
    - Microfilm Studies, Undated (Box 13, Folder 580)
    - Microfilm Vendors, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 581)
    - Microfilmers, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 582)
    - Microfilming, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 583)
    - Microlfilm Unit, 1978-1986 (Box 13, Folder 584)
    - Microfilming - Presentation at Yale and Presentation Backlog, 1984, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 585)
    - Microfilming Contract - Yale, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 586)
    - Microfilming Contracts - General, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 587)
    - Microfilming Costs, 1985, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 588)
    - Microfilming Talk, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 589)
    - Microforms, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 590)
    - Microform Cataloging, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 591)
    - Microform - International, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 592)
    - Microfilms - Consideration in Expanding, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 593)
    - Microform - Physical Handling (Betsey), 1978, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 594)
    - Microform Reading Room, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 595)
    - Microwaving, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 596)
    - Midwest Cooperative Reading Room, Undated (Box 13, Folder 597)
    - Minnesota Cooperative Pres. Program, Undated (Box 13, Folder 598)
    - Mold, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 599)
    - Monitoring, Undated (Box 13, Folder 600)
    - Mormons, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 601)
    - Morning Star, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 602)
    - MS+A, Undated (Box 13, Folder 604)
    - Mudd, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 605)
    - Mudd - Serie Set, 1984, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 606)
    - Multiple Version, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 607)
    - Mulit-volume Sets, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 608)
    - Music Library, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 609)
    - Mutilation, 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 610)
    - Mylar Encapsulation, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 611)
    - Nasara, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 612)
    - National Advisory Council on Pres., 1988, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 613)
    - National Archives, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 614)
    - National Library of Medicine, 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 615)
    - NLM - Permanent Paper, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 616)
    - NLM - Preservation Planning, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 617)
    - NEDCC, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 618)
    - NEDCC, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 619)
    - Negative Film Cataloging, 1981, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 620)
    - NEH, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 621)
    - NEH Preservation Application, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - NEH - Master Copies, 1979-1987 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - NEH Humanities Projects, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 624)
    - NEH - National Heritage Press, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 625)
    - New York State, Undated (Box 13, Folder 626)
    - New York State Preservation, 1991, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 627)
    - Newspaper Project, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 628)
    - Newspaper Standards, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 629)
    - NIC, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 630)
    - NISO, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 631)
    - NISO Environment Standard, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 632)
    - NISO Subcom R, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 633)
    - Nitrate Film, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 634)
    - Notis, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 635)
    - NRMM, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 636)
    - NUC, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 637)
    - OCLC (Online Computer Library Center), Undated (Box 13, Folder 638)
    - OCLC Microform Project, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 639)
    - OCR, Undated (Box 13, Folder 640)
    - Old Student Employ - Pres, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 641)
  - Professional Activities
    - Various papers, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 642)
    - Publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 643)
    - Recruiting, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 644)
    - No label, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 650)
    - No label, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 651)
    - Book Handling, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 662)
    - Collection Condition Survey, evolution of forms, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 663)
    - Correspondence - NEH, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 664)
    - Country Abbreviations, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 665)
    - Environmental Survey, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 666)
    - Exhibition, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 667)
    - Intern Wish Lists, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 668)
    - Intern Schedules Incomplete, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 669)
    - No label, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 670)
    - Publicity, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 671)
    - New Grant Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 672)
    - NYPL Survey, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 673)
    - Preservation Workshop, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 674)
    - Random Thoughts, Undated (Box 14, Folder 675)
    - Readers' Guide to Book Handling, Undated (Box 14, Folder 676)
    - Slide Shows, form letter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 677)
    - Slide Show, Care and Handling of Books, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 678)
    - Temperature - Conversion Table, undated (Box 14, Folder 679)
    - Slide Show, Simple Repairs for Library Materials, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 680)
    - New Slide/Tape Show, Loaned Out, Undated (Box 14, Folder 681)
    - Commercial Binding, Undated (Box 14, Folder 682)
    - Correspondence and Receipts for Slide/Tape Show, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 683)
    - History of Conservation, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 684)
    - Field Trips, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 685)
    - ARL Grant Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 686)
    - Manuals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 688)
    - Applicants, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 689)
    - RLG I - Preservation Selection CMDC/PC, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 690)
    - RLG Preservation Projects, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 691)
    - RLG Film Project, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 692)
    - Preservation in RLIN/RLG, paper-Kruger, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 693)
    - RLG Mail System, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 694)
    - Microfilms - RLG Pres. Comm., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 695)
    - RLG Online Bibliographies, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 696)
    - RLG Recon Master Neg. Cataloging, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 697)
    - Price Formula - RLG, Master Microforms PC, 1977-1982 (Box 15, Folder 698)
    - Recon Projects, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 699)
    - Pres. Union List, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 700)
    - RLG Members, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 701)
    - RLG PC - ILL, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 702)
    - Pres. Scope Notes, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 703)
    - PMP II Quarterly Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 704)
    - PMP I Quarterly Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 705)
    - PMP Cost Study, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 706)
    - Benchmarks CPMP #, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 707)
    - Collections Conservation, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 708)
    - Preservation Code in Run, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 709)
    - RLIN Costs, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 710)
    - RLG Publications, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 711)
    - Min. Pres. Oblig. RLG, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 712)
    - RLG - Primary Collecting + Preservation, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 713)
    - OCLC + RLG, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 714)
    - RLG - British Library, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 715)
    - PMP Loan Requests, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 716)
    - RLG Film Done, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 717)
    - PLMS Library Binders/Relations, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 718)
    - PLMS 1983 San Antonio (Box 15, Folder 719)
    - PLMS Physical Quality, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 720)
    - PLMS Policy + Research, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 721)
    - LC/PLMS Conferences, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Binding Pamphlets - RLMS, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - PLMS 1983 Los Angeles (Box 15, Folder 724)
    - RTSD Management for Access to Microform (Pres. Mic. Com), 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 725)
    - ALA: PADG (Pres. Admin. Disc. Group), 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 726)
    - RTSD Preservation Microfilming Committee, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 727)
    - PLMS Restructure, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 728)
    - PMP, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 729)
    - RTSD Bibliographic Control of Microfilms, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 730)
    - Pres. Educ. Directory, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 731)
    - Child, M. - Brochure Pres. Ed., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 732)
    - PLMS Education Poster, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 733)
    - PLMS Education Chicago, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 734)
    - PLMS Education, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 735)
    - Children's Bookbdg. Phip. Qual., 1982 (Box 15, Folder 736)
    - Pres. Educ. Task Force, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 737)
    - Pres. Microfilming Comm. ALA, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 738)
    - PLMS - Education, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 739)
    - Minutes, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 740)
    - Preconference, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 741)
    - Ed Com PLMS, 1979-1986 (Box 16, Folder 742)
    - ALA - PLMS, Education Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 743)
    - Agenda: Ed Com, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 744)
    - PLMS - Directory and Surveys, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 745)
    - PLMS Posters, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 746)
    - Task Force: Ed Com, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 747)
    - PLMS Ed Com - Misc, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 748)
    - PLMS - Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 749)
    - PLMS Library/Binders Task Force, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 750)
    - PLMS - Exec. Comm., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 751)
    - ALA, RTSD, PLMS - Educ. Comm., 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 752)
    - PLMS Booth, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 753)
    - PLMS - Preserv. Confs., 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 754)
    - PLMS - General Committee, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 755)
    - LBI Program Package, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 756)
    - Goals, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 757)
    - Directory, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 758)
    - Posters, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 759)
    - 1987 Preconf. Proposal (Box 16, Folder 760)
    - PLMS - Pres. Bibliogrphy, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 761)
    - RLMS, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 762)
    - 1980 Midwinter Meeting (Box 16, Folder 763)
    - Preservation Discussion Group, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 764)
    - PLMS 1981 Midwinter (Box 16, Folder 765)
    - RIT Lab, Undated (Box 16, Folder 766)
    - ALA - Personal Appointments, 1975-1980 (Box 16, Folder 767)
    - PLMC - 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 768)
    - ALA PLMC - Meetings, Minutes, Programs, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 769)
    - ALA - Mailing List Preservation, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 770)
    - Research Conference - ALA Philadelphia, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 771)
    - AAP / RTSD Joint Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 772)
    - ALA 1981 San Francisco Program (Box 16, Folder 773)
    - AAP / RTSD Joint Committee and Program, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 774)
    - ALA Booth and Towers, Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 775)
    - PLMS Library/Binders Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 776)
    - PLMS Policy and Research, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 777)
    - PLMS Appointments - 1982-1983, State Nominating Comm. - 1983-1984, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 778)
    - RTSD International Relations Committee, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 779)
    - PLMS 1983 Los Angeles (Box 16, Folder 780)
    - PLMS 1983 San Antonio (Box 16, Folder 781)
    - PLMS/LC Education Workshops, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 782)
    - Education Workshop - Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 783)
    - Physical Quality - PLMS, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 784)
    - RLG - Denver, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 785)
    - PLMS Liasons - Other Sections., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 786)
    - PLMS Library/Binders Relations, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 787)
    - Dallas Conference Planning Committee, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 788)
    - PLMS Anuual 1983 - Los Angeles (Box 16, Folder 789)
    - Preservation Microfilming ALA, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 790)
    - P+R - PLMS, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 791)
    - PLMS Policy and Planning Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 792)
    - ALA - Midwinter, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 793)
    - PLMS PA Institute Planning Com, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 794)
    - Providence ALA, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 795)
    - Pres. Micro. Committee ALCTS, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 796)
    - PLMS PADG, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 797)
    - Pres. Program Mgmt. PLMS ALA, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 798)
    - Pres. Mic. Comm. ALA, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 799)
    - BIB. Control of Micro. ALCTS, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 800)
    - ALA Microfilming Preconf., 1991 (Box 16, Folder 801)
    - NEH - Overall Training, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 802)
    - Intern Education Misc., 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 803)
    - Internships - General Yale, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 804)